Classic terror is now state-of-the-art shock.
Frankenstein Unbound is a horror, science fiction film directed by Roger Corman.
The ultimate weapon, claimed to be safe for mankind, produces global
side-effects including time slides and disappearances.
The scientist behind the project and his car are zapped from the
year 2031 to 1817 in Switzerland where he meets Dr.
Victor Frankenstein, Mary Shelley and others.
Dr. Joe Buchanan / Narrator (voice), played by John Hurt.
Dr. Victor Frankenstein, played by Raúl Juliá.
The Monster, played by Nick Brimble.
Mary Wollstonecraft Godwin, played by Bridget Fonda.
Lord George Gordon Byron, played by Jason Patric.
Percy Byshee Shelley, played by Michael Hutchence.
Frankenstein Unbound is a 1990 science fiction horror film based on Brian Aldiss's 1973 novel of the
same name, starring John Hurt, Raul Julia, Bridget Fonda, Jason Patric, and Nick Brimble.
The film is co-written and directed by Roger Corman, returning to the
director's chair after a hiatus of almost fifteen years.
This is his final film as a director before his death in 2024.
He was paid $1 million to direct.
Released by 20th Century Fox domestically and Warner Bros.
internationally.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.